Time is an illusion.
Synchronic is a horror, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Aaron Moorhead.
Two New Orleans paramedics' lives are ripped apart after encountering a series of
horrific deaths linked to a designer drug with bizarre, otherworldly effects.
Steve Denube, played by Anthony Mackie.
Dennis Dannelly, played by Jamie Dornan.
Tara Dannelly, played by Katie Aselton.
Brianna Dannelly, played by Alexia Ioannides.
Dr. Kermani, played by Ramiz Monsef.
The Looter, played by Bill Oberst Jr..
Synchronic is a 2019 American science fiction horror film directed
and produced by Justin Benson and Aaron Moorhead.
Written by Benson, the film shares continuity with other films by
Benson and Moorhead, following Resolution and The Endless.
Synchronic stars Anthony Mackie and Jamie Dornan as paramedics who investigate a
series of inexplicable deaths and their connection to a new designer drug.
It had its world premiere at the 2019 Toronto International Film Festival.
It was released on October 23, 2020, by Well Go USA Entertainment.
The film explores themes of brain tumor, new orleans,
louisiana, affectation, time travel, swamp.
The tone is intense and dark and thought_provoking.